# JONEER

# **ABOUT ME**

Along with my professional & open-source experience with software engineering, I also bring a well-rounded educational foundation with a BS in Full-Stack Web Development (4.0 GPA) and a Certificate of Full-Stack Web Development from a bootcamp. I also bring the soft-skills to integrate into any team.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **FARM BUREAU BANK**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Responsible for the development and maintenance of internal and external web applications and tools. Writes, tests, develops and implements custom programs to streamline financial institution workflows. Tech: jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL May 2019 - Present

### **CNF TECHNOLOGIES**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Responsible for developing and maintaining the full stack of a website utilized by the U.S. Air Force to maintain and track data on cryptographic products. Tech: ASP.NET, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL DataTables, Bootbox, Font Awesome & Bootstrap. Mar - Dec 2018

## **VARIOUS ORGANIZATIONS**

OPEN SOURCE SOFTWARE CONTRIBUTOR

Develops and delivers software solutions to over 20 organizations including The Apache Software Foundation, Mozilla, #VetsWhoCode, Microsoft & more. Tech: React, Docker, C#, Node.js, EJS, Tailwind CSS, Markdown, Git, Angular, TypeScript, JSON. Oct 2016 - Present

### U.S. ARMY

**SOLDIER** 

Planned, coordinated, and conducted training events in order to prepare for deploying into permissive and non-permissive environments. Trained and led teams, as Senior Enlisted Advisor and Medical Provider, on multiple deployments. Sep 2001 - Nov 2016

# CONTACT

kevinjones.engineer github.com/joneskj55 linkedin.com/in/joneskj55 joneskj55@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

### **BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY**

2020 - 2022 | BS Web Development

### **CODEUP**

2016 - 2017 | Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

# **SKILLS**

JavaScript Git
HTML CSS
Node.js React
Angular Java
Express ASP.NET
MongoDB SQL